Making money by trading in share market is
not easy but if you follow simple steps
then you can become a successful trader.
Number one you have to learn the
basics of trading. Once you learn the basic
then the second step is to
learn the strategies. You have to learn strategies and
on number three you bake them. Now after
backtesting, see which
streets have been more profitable.
After that you pick a strategy. Date
this point number four. After picking the streets,
on number five. You
start demo trading. Now in demo trading,
when the results are seen, the
next step is to do live trading.
When you trade live, after that you
create a trading plan and
continuously review your plan and this.
If you want to invest in stock market or
want to trade then
you will get the link of free demat account
in the description comment box and in the bio.
Finally you can share this video and spread
it.